export const verbPracticeDataEnglish = {
  2: [
    { prompt: "I", answer: "am" },
    { prompt: "You", answer: "are" },
    { prompt: "He", answer: "is" },
    { prompt: "She", answer: "is" },
    { prompt: "It", answer: "is" },
    { prompt: "am", answer: "I" },
    { prompt: "are", answer: "you" },
    { prompt: "is", answer: "he/she/it" }
  ],
  3: [
    { prompt: "I", answer: "have" },
    { prompt: "You", answer: "have" },
    { prompt: "He", answer: "has" },
    { prompt: "She", answer: "has" },
    { prompt: "It", answer: "has" },
    { prompt: "have", answer: "I/you" },
    { prompt: "has", answer: "he/she/it" }
  ]
};
